[
  {"question": "What happened when the computer geeks met?", 
    "answer": "It was love at first site!",
    "categories": ["computer"]},
  {"question": "Why was the computer cold at night?", 
    "answer": "It forgot to close its windows!",
    "categories": ["computer"]},
  {"question": "Why did the computer get glasses?", 
    "answer": "To improve its web sight!",
    "categories": ["computer"]},
  {"question": "How do you catch a runaway computer?", 
    "answer": "With an internet!",
    "categories": ["computer"]},
  {"question": "Why did the chicken cross the road?", 
    "answer": "To get to the other side!",
    "categories": ["chicken", "animal"]},
  {"question": "Why did the chicken cross the internet?", 
    "answer": "To get to the other site!",
    "categories": ["chicken", "animal", "computer"]},
  {"question": "Why did the chicken cross the road?", 
    "answer": "To practice social distancing!",
    "categories":  ["chicken", "animal"]},
  {"question": "Why did the horse cross the road?",
    "answer": "To get to the other NEIGH-bourhood!",
    "categories": ["horse", "animal"]},
  {"question": "Whatâ€™s it called when a snowman has a temper tantrum?",
    "answer": "A meltdown!",
    "categories": ["snow", "weather"]},
  {"question": "Why did the snowman go to the doctor?",
    "answer": "He was feeling chilled!",
    "categories": ["snow", "weather"]},
  {"question": "What do snowmen wear on their heads?",
    "answer": "Ice caps!",
    "categories": ["snow", "weather"]},
  {"question": "Why is frosty the snowman popular?",
    "answer": "He's really cool!",
    "categories": ["snow", "weather"]},
  {"question": "What do you call it when it rains chickens & ducks?",
    "answer": "Fowl weather!",
    "categories": ["rain", "chicken", "weather", "animal"]},
  {"question": "Where do you learn to make ice cream?",
    "answer": "At Sundae School!",
    "categories": ["school", "food"]},
  {"question": "What do you get when you cross a vampire with a teacher?",
    "answer": "Lots of blood tests!",
    "categories": ["school"]},
  {"question": "Why shouldn't a school be near a chicken farm?",
    "answer": "So the kids don't overhear fowl language!",
    "categories": ["school", "chicken", "animal"]},
  {"question": "What is a runner's favourite subject in school?",
    "answer": "Jog-raphy!",
    "categories": ["school", "running", "fitness"]},
  {"question": "Why did the square and triangle go to the gym?",
    "answer": "To stay in shape!",
    "categories": ["fitness"]},
  {"question": "What do race car drivers eat?",
    "answer": "Fast food!",
    "categories": ["food"]},
  {"question": "What do you call a bear standing in the rain?",
    "answer": "A drizzly bear!",
    "categories": ["animal", "rain", "weather"]},
  {"question": "What do you call a bear standing in the rain?",
    "answer": "A drizzly bear!",
    "categories": ["animal", "rain", "weather"]},
  {"question": "What bow can't be tied?",
    "answer": "A rainbow!",
    "categories": ["rain", "weather"]},
  {"question": "What happened when the cheese factory exploded in France?",
    "answer": "There was de Brie everywhere!",
    "categories": ["food"]},
  {"question": "What happened when the teacher tied all the kids' shoe laces together?",
    "answer": "They had a class trip!",
    "categories": ["school"]},  
  {"question": "How did the computer hacker get out of jail?",
    "answer": "He pressed the escape key!",
    "categories": ["computer"]},
  {"question": "Why did the chicken cross the playground?",
    "answer": "To get to the other slide!",
    "categories": ["chicken", "animal"]},
  {"question": "Why did Cinderella fail gym class?",
    "answer": "She kept running away from the ball!",
    "categories": ["running", "fitness", "school","sports"]},
  {"question": "Why do mother kangaroos hate rainy days?",
    "answer": "Because the kids have to play inside!",
    "categories": ["rain", "weather", "mom", "animal"]},
  {"question": "What did the mommy rope say to the baby rope?",
    "answer": "Don't be knotty!",
    "categories": ["mom"]},
  {"question": "Why did the monster's mother knit him 3 socks?",
    "answer": "Because he grew another foot!",
    "categories": ["mom"]},
  {"question": "What did the baby corn say to the mama corn?",
    "answer": "Where is Popcorn!",
    "categories": ["mom", "food", "dad"]},
  {"question": "What did the beach say as the tide came in?",
    "answer": "Long time no sea!",
    "categories": ["beach", "vacation"]},
  {"question": "Why do magician's do really well at school?",
    "answer": "Because they're good at the trick questions!",
    "categories": ["school"]},
  {"question": "Why can't basketball players go on summer vacation?",
    "answer": "They'd get called for travelling!",
    "categories": ["basketball","sports", "fitness"]},
  {"question": "Why did the basketball player bring a glass of water to gym?",
    "answer": "So he could learn to dribble!",
    "categories": ["basketball","sports", "fitness", "school"]},
  {"question": "What's the problem with twin witches?",
    "answer": "You can't tell which witch is which!",
    "categories": ["halloween"]},
  {"question": "Why don't skeletons like parties?",
    "answer": "They have no body to dance with!",
    "categories": ["halloween"]},
  {"question": "Why don't fish go on vacation?",
    "answer": "Because they're always in school!",
    "categories": ["school", "animal", "vacation"]},
  {"question": "Why did the boy wear glasses during Math class?",
    "answer": "Because it improves di-vision!",
    "categories": ["school", "math"]},
  {"question": "What is a Math teacher's favourite dessert?",
    "answer": "Pi!",
    "categories": ["food", "math", "school"]},
  {"question": "Why was the Math book sad?",
    "answer": "Because it had so many problems!",
    "categories": ["math", "school"]},
  {"question": "How do you get straight A's?",
    "answer": "With a ruler!",
    "categories": ["math", "school"]},
  {"question": "What did the golfer dad want for Father's Day?",
    "answer": "A tee shirt!",
    "categories": ["golf", "dad", "sports", "fitness"]},
  {"question": "Why do golfers carry an extra pair of socks?",
    "answer": "In case they get a hole in one!",
    "categories": ["golf", "sports", "fitness"]},
  {"question": "Why don't eggs tell jokes?",
    "answer": "They would crack each other up!",
    "categories": ["food"]},
  {"question": "What did the baker say when he found the dough he'd lost?",
    "answer": "That's just what I kneaded!",
    "categories": ["food"]},
  {"question": "How long does it take to count four times infinity?",
    "answer": "Four-ever!",
    "categories": ["math", "school"]},
  {"question": "What do you get from a nervous cow?",
    "answer": "A milkshake",
    "categories": ["food", "animal"]},
  {"question": "What does a mixed-up hen lay?",
    "answer": "Scrambled eggs!",
    "categories": ["food","animal"]},
  {"question": "Why does the mushroom have so many friends?",
    "answer": "Because he's a fungi!",
    "categories": ["food"]}
]